[
	{
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ア?",
		"answers": ["a"]
	},
	{
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: イ?",
		"answers": ["i"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ウ?",
		"answers": ["u"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: エ?",
		"answers": ["e"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: オ?",
		"answers": ["o"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: カ?",
		"answers": ["ka"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: キ?",
		"answers": ["ki"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ク?",
		"answers": ["ku"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ケ?",
		"answers": ["ke"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: コ?",
		"answers": ["ko"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: サ?",
		"answers": ["sa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: シ?",
		"answers": ["shi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ス?",
		"answers": ["su"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: セ?",
		"answers": ["se"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ソ?",
		"answers": ["so"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: タ?",
		"answers": ["ta"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: チ?",
		"answers": ["chi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ツ?",
		"answers": ["tsu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: テ?",
		"answers": ["te"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ト?",
		"answers": ["to"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ナ?",
		"answers": ["na"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ニ?",
		"answers": ["ni"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヌ?",
		"answers": ["nu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ネ?",
		"answers": ["ne"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ノ?",
		"answers": ["no"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ハ?",
		"answers": ["ha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヒ?",
		"answers": ["hi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: フ?",
		"answers": ["fu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヘ?",
		"answers": ["he"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ホ?",
		"answers": ["ho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: マ?",
		"answers": ["ma"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ミ?",
		"answers": ["mi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ム?",
		"answers": ["mu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: メ?",
		"answers": ["me"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: モ?",
		"answers": ["mo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヤ?",
		"answers": ["ya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ユ?",
		"answers": ["yu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヨ?",
		"answers": ["yo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ラ?",
		"answers": ["ra"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: リ?",
		"answers": ["ri"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ル?",
		"answers": ["ru"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: レ?",
		"answers": ["re"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ロ?",
		"answers": ["ro"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ワ?",
		"answers": ["wa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ヲ?",
		"answers": ["wo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What basic katakana is this: ン?",
		"answers": ["n"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ガ?",
		"answers": ["ga"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ギ?",
		"answers": ["gi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: グ?",
		"answers": ["gu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ゲ?",
		"answers": ["ge"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ゴ?",
		"answers": ["go"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ザ?",
		"answers": ["za"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ジ?",
		"answers": ["ji"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ズ?",
		"answers": ["zu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ゼ?",
		"answers": ["ze"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ゾ?",
		"answers": ["zo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ダ?",
		"answers": ["da"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ヂ?",
		"answers": ["ji"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ヅ?",
		"answers": ["zu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: デ?",
		"answers": ["de"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ド?",
		"answers": ["do"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: バ?",
		"answers": ["ba"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ビ?",
		"answers": ["bi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ブ?",
		"answers": ["bu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ベ?",
		"answers": ["be"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ボ?",
		"answers": ["bo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: パ?",
		"answers": ["pa"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ピ?",
		"answers": ["pi"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: プ?",
		"answers": ["pu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ペ?",
		"answers": ["pe"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What voiced katakana is this: ポ?",
		"answers": ["po"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: キャ?",
		"answers": ["kya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: キュ?",
		"answers": ["kyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: キョ?",
		"answers": ["kyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: シャ?",
		"answers": ["sha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: シュ?",
		"answers": ["shu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ショ?",
		"answers": ["sho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: チャ?",
		"answers": ["cha"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: チュ?",
		"answers": ["chu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: チョ?",
		"answers": ["cho"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ニャ?",
		"answers": ["nya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ニュ?",
		"answers": ["nyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ニョ?",
		"answers": ["nyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ヒャ?",
		"answers": ["hya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ヒュ?",
		"answers": ["hyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ヒョ?",
		"answers": ["hyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ミャ?",
		"answers": ["mya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ミュ?",
		"answers": ["myu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ミョ?",
		"answers": ["myo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: リャ?",
		"answers": ["rya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: リュ?",
		"answers": ["ryu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: リョ?",
		"answers": ["ryo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ギャ?",
		"answers": ["gya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ギュ?",
		"answers": ["gyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ギョ?",
		"answers": ["gyo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ジャ?",
		"answers": ["ja"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ジュ?",
		"answers": ["ju"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ジョ?",
		"answers": ["jo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ビャ?",
		"answers": ["bya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ビュ?",
		"answers": ["byu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ビョ?",
		"answers": ["byo"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ピャ?",
		"answers": ["pya"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ピュ?",
		"answers": ["pyu"]
    },
    {
		"question": "What combo katakana is this: ピョ?",
		"answers": ["pyo"]
    }
]